Guide to the Divinity School Records, circa 1920-2005 UA.19.01.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Administrative Files, circa 1920-2005; 156 Linear Feet; 109 boxes
  - Accession A83-86
    - Nease, Edgar H., 1968-1970 (Box 29)
    - National Cooperative Enlistment Project, 1968-1970 (Box 29)
    - O - Correspondence, Dean Cushman, 1968-1970 (Box 29)
    - P - Correspondence, Dean Cushman, 1968-1971 (Box 29)
    - Q - Correspondence, Dean Cushman, 1967-1970 (Box 29)
    - R - Correspondence, Dean Cushman, 1968-1971 (Box 29)
    - S - Correspondence, Dean Cushman, 1968-1971 (Box 29)
    - Schaller, Lyle E., 1971 (Box 29)
    - St. John's Methodist Church, 1969 (Box 29)
    - St. Michael's Parish, Dumfries, Scotland, 1960-1970 (Box 29)
    - Sharpe, John L. III, 1970-1971 (Box 29)
    - Samuel, Dr. Karriappa, 1967 (Box 29)
    - S.I.E.C.U.S - General Information, 1969 (Box 29)
    - S.A.C.S., 1965 (Box 29)
    - Student Representative Assembly, Miscellaneous, 1969-1973 (Box 29)
    - T - Correspondence, Dean Cushman, 1968-1971 (Box 29)
    - Tavernisi Clippings, 1966-1967 (Box 29)
    - Theological Faculty Fellowship Applications, 1961-1971 (Box 29)
    - U - Correspondence, Dean Cushman, 1969-1970 (Box 29)
    - U.S. Government Correspondence, 1961-1969 (Box 29)
    - V - Correspondence, Dean Cushman, 1969 (Box 29)
    - W - Correspondence, Dean Cushman, 1968-1971 (Box 29)
    - Weingart, Richard E., 1968-1969 (Box 29)
    - West Market Street Methodist Church, 1969 (Box 29)
    - X, Y, Z - Correspondence, Dean Cushman, 1967-1970 (Box 29)
    - Personnel Index, 1966-1970 (Box 29)
    - Admissions and Recruitment, 1969-1971 (Box 29)
    - Divinity School Policy (Advancement and Tenure) 1961-1963 (Box 29)
    - Master of Sacred Music Degree Study, undated (Box 29)
    - Admission of Negroes, 1951-1961 (Box 29)
    - Correspondence Re: Admittance of Blacks to the Divinity School, 1954-1961 (Box 29)
    - Student Protest - Segregation Policy, 1959-1960 (Box 29)
    - Report: Negro Theological Education, 1961 (Box 29)
    - Clippings/Media Re: Integration, 1956-1961 (Box 29)
    - Negro Recruitment, 1961 (Box 29)
    - Desegregation and the Church, 1961 (Box 29)
    - Raymond Cooke - Student in CH. I, 1969-1970 (Box 29)
    - Appointment - Historical Division, 1973 (Box 29)
    - Appointments in Church History, 1970-1972 (Box 29)
    - Reformation Church History Appointments, 1963-1973 (Box 29)
    - Old Testament Appointment, 1970 (Box 29)
    - History Theology Appointments, 1969-1970 (Box 29)
    - Christian Education Appointment, 1972-1973 (Box 29)
    - Inquiries Re: Appointments, 1969-1972 (Box 29)
    - Applicants Seeking Appointments, 1968 (Box 29)
    - Black Staffing and Faculty, 1969-1971 (Box 29)
    - Director of Admissions and Student Life, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Field Education Staffing, 1969-1972 (Box 29)
    - American Church History, 1961-1971 (Box 29)
    - Continuing Ed. Personnel, 1968-1972 (Box 29)
    - Missions and Comparative Religion, 1971 (Box 29)
    - Negro Staff and Academic Personnel, 1969-1971 (Box 29)
    - New Testament Appointments, 1970-1971 (Box 29)
    - Old Testament Appointments, 1968-1971 (Box 30)
    - Pastoral Care Appointments, 1969-1970 (Box 30)
    - Preaching Appointment, 1972-1973 (Box 30)
    - Applied Sociology of Religion Appointment, 1959-1970 (Box 30)
    - Speech, Drama, Sacred Music, 1966-1970 (Box 30)
    - Systematic Theology, 1964-1972 (Box 30)
  - Accession A90-63
    Administrative records are restricted for 25 years from their date of origin. Please contact Research Services for more information.
    - Christian Advocate, 1972-1975 (Box 30)
    - Fayettville - NCC Higher Education, 1976 (Box 30)
    - Minutes of Committee on Continuing Education, 1978 (Box 30)
    - Board of Evangelism, 1969 (Box 30)
    - Western North Carolina Conference, 1976-1980 (2 Folders) (Box 30)
    - Board of Ordained Ministry Minutes, 1979 (Box 30)
    - Division of Higher Education - North Carolina Conference, Louisburg College, 1977 (Box 30)
    - Western North Carolina Conference - Board of the Ministry, 1976-1980 (2 Folders) (Box 30)
    - NC Conference in Campus Ministry, 1979 (Box 30)
    - Division of Higher Education - North Carolina Conference, N.C. Wesleyan College, 1977-1979 (Box 30)
    - WNC Annual Conference - Lake Junaluska, 1977 (Box 30)
    - Visiting Annual Conference Representatives, 1977-1978 (Box 30)
    - Lay Leaders, 1971-1972 (Box 30)
    - Ordination and Special Appointment, 1974-1975 (2 Folders) (Box 30)
    - Virginia Annual Conference, 1972-1978 (Box 30)
    - Mission to Ministers - Charlotte, N.C., 1976-1977 (Box 30)
    - WNC - Journal of 1972 Session, 1972 (Box 30)
    - Conference Committee on Continuing Ed., 1972-1979 (Box 30)
    - Annual Conference Visitation, Divinity School, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Alumni Meetings - Annual Conferences, 1976-1978 (Box 30)
    - Joint Higher Education Committee Minutes, 1976 (Box 30)
    - Holston Conference, 1979-1980 (Box 30)
    - Reports on Students to Annual Conferences, 1976 (Box 30)
    - Ministerial Appointments, WVA Conference, 1977 (Box 30)
    - Communications, Annual Conferences, 1973-1974 (Box 30)
    - Annual Conferences Miscellaneous, 1974-1980 (2 Folders) (Box 30)
    - Dr. Robert W. Thornburg - Board of Higher Education and Ministry, Division of Ordained Ministry, 1974-1978 (3 Folders) (Box 30)
    - Chicago, 1979 (Box 30)
    - Center for Academic Societies and Religion, 1974-1975 (Box 30)
    - WNC Appointments, 1979-1980 (Box 30)
    - Ritchie, Baxter Maurice, 1973-1982 (2 Folders) (Box 31)
    - Robinson, Charles K., 1962-1982 (Box 31)
    - Robinson Course Material - CT 110, 1962, undated (2 Folders) (Box 31)
    - Robinson Course Material - CC102 and CC229, undated (Box 31)
    - Smith, Harmon L., 1962-1982 (3 Folders) (Box 31)
    - Smith, D. Moody, 1971-1982 (Box 31)
    - Smith, H. Shelton, 1955-1987 RESTRICTED (Box 31)
    - Steinmetz, David C., 1969-1982 (2 Folders) (Box 31)
    - Weldon, O. Wilson, 1971-1982 (Box 31)
    - Willimon, William, 1976-1981 (Box 31)
    - Westerhoff, John, 1973-1982 (2 Folders) (Box 31)
    - Wilson, Robert L., 1971-1983 (3 Folders) (Box 31)
    - Young, Franklin W., 1969-1982 (Box 31)
  - Accession A90-68
    - Bureau of Public Information - L. Whitefield, 1961-1970 (Box 32)
    - Conversations with Dr. Price Re: the Divinity School and the Dept. of Religion, 1964 (Box 32)
    - Powell, Dr. Benjamin - Librarian, 1953-1974 (Box 32)
    - Tuthill, R.I., 1954-1967 (Box 32)
    - Whitford, W.E., 1958-1965 (Box 32)
    - Younts, Worth D., 1969-1970 (Box 32)
    - Wilkinson, Howard C., 1959-1972 (Box 32)
    - Academic Council, 1967-1976 (5 Folders) (Box 32)
    - Academic Administrative Personnel, 1961-1970 (Box 32)
    - University Bequest Program, undated (Box 32)
    - University Committee on Financial Aid, 1968 (Box 32)
    - Committee on Baccalaureate Preachers, 1961-1963 (Box 32)
    - University By-Laws, undated (Box 32)
    - Univeristy Christian Movement, undated (Box 32)
    - Committee on Education Administration - Minutes, 1962-1971 (Box 32)
    - Commonwealth Values Project, 1974 (Box 32)
    - Duke University Credit Union, 1968 (Box 32)
    - Cooperative Program in the Humanities, 1965-1969 (Box 32)
    - Design Study, Duke University, 1963 (Box 32)
    - Educational Administration Advisory Board Minutes, 1969-1972 (Box 32)
    - Committee on Graduate Center, 1963 (Box 32)
    - Duke Humanities Council, 1968-1976 (Box 32)
    - Office of Institutional Studies Survey, 1966 (Box 32)
    - International Students, 1966 (Box 32)
    - Committee on International Students, 1968-1969 (Box 32)
    - Maids and Janitors - Local Union 77, 1965-1966 (Box 32)
    - University Chaplain (Search Committee), 1972-1973 (Box 32)
    - Duke Univ. NROTC Program, 1969 (Box 32)
    - Placement Service - Duke Univ., 1969-1970 (Box 32)
    - Presidential Search Committee, 1969 (Box 32)
    - Duke University Provost's Report, 1966-1968 (Box 32)
    - Six Associates, 1969-1972 (Box 32)
    - Shelter Management Course, 1962 (Box 32)
    - Football Weekends, 1975-1981 (Box 32)
    - Divinity School Fellowship, 1972-1977 (4 Folders) (Box 32)
    - WNC Meeting, 1974 (Box 32)
    - Fellowship Meeting, 1976 (Box 32)
    - A-M General Files, 1964-1972 (2 Folders) (Box 33)
    - Affirmative Action Plan for Equal Employment Opportunity, 1970-1974 (Box 33)
    - Alumni Affairs - Charles Umberger, 1973-1976 (Box 33)
    - Alumni Campaign, 1965-1970 (Box 33)
    - Alumni Dinner, 1972 (Box 33)
    - Alumni Misc., 1961-1975 (2 Folders) (Box 33)
    - Alumni News, 1974-1975 (Box 33)
    - Alumni Newsletter, 1961-1966 (Box 33)
    - Alumni Secretary, M. Laney Funderburk, 1965-1973 (Box 33)
    - Anlyan, William G., 1965-1969 (Box 33)
    - Annual Conference Visitation, 1973-1975 (Box 33)
    - Alumni Visitor's Week, 1968-1970 (Box 33)
    - Ashmore, Mr. Frank L., 1962-1970 (Box 33)
    - Baccalaureate Sermon, 1971 (Box 33)
    - Ball, Dean Margaret, 1964 (Box 33)
    - Bowers, H. F., 1960-1974 (Box 33)
    - Bryson, E. C., 1957-1970 (Box 33)
    - Charlesworth, James, 1972-1976 (3 Folders) (Box 33)
    - Clyde, Dr. Paul H., 1961 (Box 33)
    - Cooper, W. G. - Employment Office, 1963-1965 (Box 33)
    - Cushman Testimonial Dinner, 1971 (Box 33)
    - Cushman Resignation, 1970-1971 (2 Folders) (Box 33)
    - Frenzel, Charles H., 1963-1965 (Box 33)
    - Goodwin, Craufurd D., 1963-1970 (Box 33)
    - Henricksen, G. C., 1959-1969 (Box 33)
    - Hopkins, Dr. Everett, 1960-1966 (Box 33)
    - Howard, W. K., 1960-1965 (Box 33)
    - Loyalty Fund Contributions, 1971-1974 (Box 33)
    - N-Z General Files, 1966-1972 (Box 33)
    - Phillips, J. H. - University Marshall, 1966-1970 (Box 33)
    - Predmore, Dean R. L., 1961-1969 (Box 33)
    - Price, Dr. James L., 1960-1965 (Box 33)
    - Western North Carolina Conference, 1966-1976 (2 Folders) (Box 34)
    - Baltimore Annual Conference, 1961-1976 (Box 34)
    - Conference Visitations, 1969-1972 (Box 34)
    - North Alabama Conference, 1959-1975 (Box 34)
    - Florida Annual Conference, 1962-1974 (Box 34)
    - Nebraska Annual Conference, 1961-1974 (Box 34)
    - Holston Annual Conference, 1972-1976 (Box 34)
    - The Virginia Conference, 1959-1976 (Box 34)
    - Fund for Reconciliation - N.C. Conference, undated (Box 34)
    - Pastors' School - Tennessee Conference, 1972 (Box 34)
    - South Carolina Annual Conference - 1959-1976 (Box 34)
    - West Virginia Conference, 1969-1975 (Box 34)
    - The Reverend N.W. Grant, 1970-1972 (Box 34)
    - The North Carolina Conference, 1958-1976 (8 Folders) (Box 34)
    - N.C. United Methodists Commission on Continuing Education for Ministers, 1966-1973 (Box 34)
    - Pastoral Ministry Meeting, 1972 (Box 34)
    - Seminars - Correspondence, 1956-1967 (Box 34)
    - Div. School Symposium: The Task of Theology Today, 1966-1968 (2 Folders) (Box 34)
    - Duke Div. School Seminars, 1969-1970 (Box 34)
    - South Carolina and Virginia Seminars, 1972 (Box 34)
    - Trigg, James D., 1961-1971 (Box 34)
    - A-H, General Files, 1973-1976 (2 Folders) (Box 34)
    - I-Z, General Files, 1973-1976 (Box 34)
    - Lee, Billy F., 1972 (Box 35)
    - Dean's Annual Report to the President, 1950-1962 (Box 35)
    - In Absentia Degrees, 1971 (Box 35)
    - Student Correspondence, A-M, 1970-1976 (2 Folders) (Box 35)
    - Student Correspondence, N-Z, 1970-1976 (Box 35)
    - Student Association, 1969-1972 (Box 35)
    - Student Constitution, 1947, 1961 (Box 35)
    - Student Pastors and Assistant, 1966-1967 (Box 35)
    - The Divinity School Student Government Association, 1960-1968 (Box 35)
    - Coordinating Council, 1965-1969 (Box 35)
    - Student Government Association, 1963-1964 (Box 35)
    - Duke Chronicle, 1968-1969 (Box 35)
    - Area Concentration Exams, 1967 (Box 35)
    - Association of Methodist Seminary Students, 1968 (Box 35)
    - Student Pastors, 1969-1970 (Box 35)
    - Chapel Worship, 1968 (Box 35)
    - Coordinating Council, 1968 (Box 35)
    - Hannavee, 1970 (Box 35)
    - Div. School Application, undated (Box 35)
    - Methodist Student Movement, 1958-1962 (Box 35)
    - Divinity Student Military Service, 1966 (Box 35)
    - S.G.A. Business, 1961-1963 (Box 35)
    - Housing for Graduate and Professional Students, 1960-1972 (Box 35)
    - Response, 1972 (Box 35)
    - Essay Contest, 1962 (Box 35)
    - Senior Class Picture, undated (Box 35)
    - Student Government Officers, 1952-1963 (Box 35)
    - Summer Language Institute, 1965 (Box 35)
    - Student Withdrawal, 1969 (Box 35)
    - Library Expansion and Divinity, 1962-1970 (Box 35)
    - Library - Farris, 1959-1971 (Box 35)
    - ATLA Fellowship Program, 1968 (Box 35)
    - All-University Opening Convocation, 1964-1966 (Box 35)
    - Summer Clinics, 1969-1974 (Box 35)
    - Clinics, Misc., 1963-1968 (Box 35)
    - Clinic in Preaching, 1964-1967 (Box 35)
    - Pastoral Care Clinics, 1961-1963 (Box 35)
    - Summer Clinics, 1971 (Box 35)
    - Approved Supply Pastors' School, 1951-1969 (Box 35)
    - Annual Faculty Lecturer, 1961-1966 (Box 35)
    - Lectures, 1957-1971 (3 Folders) (Box 35)
    - Library Lectures and Reports, 1958-1969 (Box 35)
    - Public Lectures - Misc. Correspondence, 1965 (Box 35)
    - Orientation, 1970 (Box 35)
    - Divinity School Opening Convocation, 1948-1968 (Box 35)
    - Duke University Conference on the Ministry, 1966-1967 (Box 35)
    - Symposium on Christian Missions, 1951-1971, (2 Folders) (Box 35)
    - Divinity School Seminars, 1956-1969 (2 Folders) (Box 35)
    - Sanders, Gordon, 1974-1978 (Box 36)
    - Quinn, Wylie Van S., 1975 (Box 36)
    - Garcia, Ofelia, 1974-1975 (Box 36)
    - Rankin, William W., 1976 (Box 36)
    - Graduate Students, 1974-1980 (Box 36)
    - Convocation on the Ministry, 1976-1977 (Box 36)
    - Memo to Advisees, 1979-1980 (Box 36)
    - Theology Weekend, 1976-1977 (Box 36)
    - Colloquy on the Loss and Recovery of the Sacred, 1979 (2 Folders) (Box 36)
    - Ministries with the Aging, 1975 (Box 36)
    - Association for Christian Training and Service (ACTS), 1969-1971 (Box 36)
    - DACUS Plaque Unveiling, 1976 (Box 36)
    - Divinity School Seminars, 1964-1966 (Box 36)
    - Ecumenical Seminar, 1963-1964 (Box 36)
    - Neville, Gwen Kennedy, 1974-1977 (Box 36)
    - SNTS Meeting, 1976 (Box 36)
    - Trinity College, Deerfield, Illinois, 1976 (Box 36)
    - Memorial United Methodist Church, Thomasville, N.C., 1979 (Box 36)
    - White, Leland, 1972-1978 (Box 36)
    - Biographical Info. - Misc. People, 1971 (Box 36)
    - Bibliographies, Miscellaneous People, 1972 (Box 36)
    - The Duke Endowment, 1969-1978 (4 Folders) (Box 36)
    - Misc. Papers, 1964-1977 (3 Folders) (Box 36)
    - Continuing Education, 1971-1976 (2 Folders) (Box 36)
  - Accession A90-78
    Administrative records are restricted for 25 years from date of origin. Please contact Research Services for more information.
    - A - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 37)
    - B - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (3 Folders) (Box 37)
    - C - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (2 Folders) (Box 37)
    - Center for Religion and Psychiatry, 1977 (Box 37)
    - Cokesbury Bookstore, 1978-1981 (Box 37)
    - D - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 37)
    - E - Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 37)
    - F - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 37)
    - Fund for Theological Education, Inc., 1978-1983 (Box 37)
    - G - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 37)
    - H - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (2 Folders) (Box 37)
    - Hanes, Gordon, 1975 (Box 37)
    - Hatchett, Mrs. Hines, 1973-1978 (Box 37)
    - I - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 37)
    - Consortium for International and/or Intercultural Theological Education, 1980-1986 (Box 37)
    - J - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 37)
    - President Major J. Jones, Gammon Theological Seminary, 1969-1983 (Box 37)
    - K - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (2 Folders) (Box 37)
    - Kidd, Jim, 1985 (Box 37)
    - L - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (2 Folders) (Box 37)
    - Laney, President James T. (Emory Univeristy), 1969-1982 (Box 37)
    - M - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (2 Folders) (Box 37)
    - Mafico, Dr. Temba J., 1983-1984 (Box 37)
    - Messer, Donald E., 1981-1982 (Box 37)
    - The Ministry of Preaching - International Growth Center, 1982-1985 (Box 37)
    - Mc - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 37)
    - National Capital Semester for Seminarians, 1982 (Box 37)
    - N - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 38)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1975-1978 (Box 38)
    - Nausner, Dr. Helmut, 1978-1981 (Box 38)
    - P - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (2 Folders) (Box 38)
    - O - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 38)
    - Outler, Albert, 1973-1989 (Box 38)
    - Q - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 38)
    - R - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 38)
    - Ramsey, Paul, 1986-1988 (Box 38)
    - S - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (3 Folders) (Box 38)
    - Southeastern Baptist Seminary, 1970-1981 (2 Folders) (Box 38)
    - T - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 38)
    - U - Correspondence, 1981-1988 (Box 38)
    - United Church of Christ, 1972-1981 (Box 38)
    - The Upper Room, 1977-1981 (Box 38)
    - V - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (Box 38)
    - W - Correspondence, 1981-1984 (2 Folders) (Box 38)
    - Academic Council, 1981-1985 (2 Folders) (Box 38)
    - Association of Theological Schools Meeting - Kansas City, MO. (Box 38)
    - Holston Alumni Dinner, 1985 (Box 38)
    - Association of Theological Schools Meeting - Pittsburgh, PA., 1984 (Box 38)
    - Association of Theological Schools - Visitation, 1984 (Box 38)
    - Consultation on Information Systems, Lilly Endowment, Indianapolis, 1985 (Box 38)
    - AUMTS Meeting, Orlando, Fl., 1984 (Box 38)
    - AUMTS Meeting, 1985 (Box 38)
    - AUMTS Meeting, Witchita, KS, 1985 (Box 39)
    - Professor Colin Blaydon, Vice Provost for Academic Policy and Planning, 1981-1983 (Box 39)
    - Orientation - SEJ Boards of Ordained Ministry, Atlanta, GA, 1984 (Box 39)
    - Kohler, Dr. Robert, Board oh Higher Education, 1980-1982 (Box 39)
    - Center for the Study of the Ancient Near Eastern Civilization and Christian Origins, 1981-1982 (Box 39)
    - Butters, Tom, 1983 (Box 39)
    - Deans Council, 1982-1986 (2 Folders) (Box 39)
    - Friedl, Dr. Ernstine, 1980-1985 (Box 39)
    - Henderson, R. James, 1977-1987 (Box 39)
    - Huestis, Charles B., 1972-1983 (Box 39)
    - Jones, Barney, 1953-1986 (Box 39)
    - Joerg, Frederick C., 1978-1980 (Box 39)
    - Society of Christian Ethics, 1985-1986 (Box 39)
    - Academic Management System, 1983 (Box 39)
    - Alumni Affairs, 1981 (Box 39)
    - Appendix C and M, 1984-1985 (Box 39)
    - Bevan, William, 1982-1983 (Box 39)
    - Bindewald, Richard A., 1968-1980 (Box 39)
    - Brooke, Harrison, 1983 (Box 39)
    - Bursar's Office, 1959-1983 (Box 39)
    - Cahow, Clark, 1968-1983 (Box 39)
    - Council on Aging and Humand Development, 1980-1981 (Box 39)
    - Computer Project, 1982 (Box 39)
    - Duke United Campus Ministry, 1983 (Box 39)
    - Faculty Notices, 1982-1983 (Box 39)
    - Equal Opportunity Employment, 1977-1984 (Box 39)
    - Gothic Bookstore, 1976-1978 (Box 39)
    - Founders' Society, 1982-1984 (Box 39)
    - Griffith, William, 1967-1982 (Box 39)
    - Honorary Degrees, 1966-1977 (Box 39)
    - Harward, Stephen C., 1963-1986 (Box 39)
    - Energy Management Report, 1970-1981 (Box 39)
    - Office of Special Events, 1979-1981 (Box 39)
    - Office of Management and Budget, 1979 (Box 39)
    - Olan Petty Summer Sessions, 1962-1975 (Box 39)
    - Research Council, 1956-1971 (Box 39)
    - Joint Religion/Divinity Council, 1976-1977 (Box 39)
    - Religious Life Council, 1980-1981 (Box 39)
    - Salinger, Marion, 1981-1982 (Box 39)
    - Wade, Charles B., Jr., 1972 (Box 39)
    - Ward, Calvin L., 1980-1985 (Box 39)
    - Wilson, O. Dean (Tel-Com), 1980 (Box 39)
    - Div. School Faculty Notices, 1981-1982 (Box 39)
    - Misc. Committee Member Lists, 1981 (Box 39)
    - Faculty Conduct Code, 1981-1982 (Box 39)
    - Publications, 1981 (Box 39)
    - Statements to the Faculty (Dean Jones), 1982 (Box 39)
    - Faculty Minutes, 1981-1982 (Box 39)
    - FEC and EAC Ballots, 1982 (Box 39)
    - Faculty Executive Council, 1980 (Box 39)
    - Educational Affairs Council, 1981-1983 (Box 39)
    - Faculty Newsletter, 1983 (Box 39)
    - General Faculty of the University Minutes, 1981 (Box 39)
    - Graduate and Professional Student Council, 1981-1986 (Box 39)
    - Green, Bill, 1979-1986 (Box 39)
    - Marshall, Roger L., 1982-1986 (Box 39)
    - Personnel, University Policy, 1980 (Box 39)
    - Methodist Interactive Database System, 1982 (Box 40)
    - Pre-Divinity Program, 1982 (Box 40)
    - President's Box, 1983-1985 (Box 40)
    - President Terry Sanford, 1982-1984 (Box 40)
    - Research Council, 1975-1982 (Box 40)
    - Sexual Harrassment Policies, 1981-1985 (Box 40)
    - Smart Family/Terry Sanford Endowment Announcement and Dinner, 1984 (Box 40)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting Minutes, 1983-1987 RESTRICTED (Box 40)
    - Duke University Trustees and Endowment, 1960-1983 (2 Folders) RESTRICTED (Box 40)
    - Director of Admissions and Student Affairs, 1973 (Box 40)
    - Ross, J. David - Office of Development, 1971-1977 (2 Folders) (Box 40)
    - Divinity School Committees, 1977-1979 (2 Folders) (Box 40)
    - Faculty Retreats, 1978-1979 (Box 40)
    - East Campus Ballroom Dinner, 1979 (Box 40)
    - Blackburn, John O., 1970-1979 (Box 40)
    - Cleaveland, Frederic N., 1971-1978 (2 Folders) (Box 40)
    - McNabb, John T., II, 1977-1976 (Box 40)
    - Meier, Otto, Jr., 1971-1974 (Box 40)
    - Robell, Paul A., 1975-1976 (Box 40)
    - Chase, Carole F., 1972-1976 (Box 40)
    - Dietz, John, undated (Box 40)
    - Harper, Lea, 1973-1976 (Box 40)
    - Sapp, Stephen, undated (Box 40)
    - Shoemaker, Stephen, undated (Box 40)
    - Lattimore, Vergel L., III, 1978 (Box 40)
    - McClain, William B., 1977-1978 (Box 40)
    - NCC and WNC Cabinets, 1976 (Box 40)
    - Self-Study Report - The Divinity School, 1976 (Box 40)
    - Gunn, Janet, 1977-1979 (Box 40)
    - Re: Lonnie Edmonson, 1976 (Box 40)
    - Greenlaw, William, 1972-1979 (Box 40)
    - Johnston, Robert Kent, 1973-1979 (Box 40)
    - Thaler, F. Roger, 1971-1976 (Box 40)
    - Re: Homelitics Poisition, 1978 (Box 40)
    - Hoffelt, R. David, 1978 (Box 40)
    - Correspondence Re: Professor of Homelitics Position, 1977-1979 (Box 40)
    - Formation of Divinity School Board of Visitors, 1963-1966 (Box 41)
    - Board of Visitors - Meeting, 1974-1977 (Box 41)
    - Board of Visitors - Meeting, 1973 (Box 41)
    - Board of Visitors - Meeting, 1972 (Box 41)
    - Board of Visitors - Meeting, 1970 (Box 41)
    - Board of Visitors - Meeting, 1969 (3 Folders) (Box 41)
    - Board of Visitors - Meeting, 1968 (Box 41)
    - Board of Visitors - Meeting, 1967 (Box 41)
    - Board of Visitors - Meeting, 1966 (Box 41)
    - Board of Visitors - Meeting, 1965 (Box 41)
    - Board of Visitors - Meeting, 1964 (2 Folders) (Box 41)
    - Board of Visitors - Miscellaneous, 1963-1978 (2 Folders) (Box 41)
    - Student Representative Assembly, 1971-1983 (2 Folders) (Box 41)
    - The Danforth Foundation, 1972 (2 Folders) (Box 41)
    - Listing of Funds - Code Info., 1966 (Box 41)
    - Divinity School Bequests and Trust Committee, 1982 (Box 42)
    - The Review of Books and Religion, 1983-1987 (Box 42)
    - Bradshaw Committee, 1978-1982 (Box 42)
    - Communion Study Committee, 1982 (Box 42)
    - Director of Continuing Education at the Divinity School Appointment Announcement, 1984 (Box 42)
    - Curriculum, 1981-1983 (Box 42)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1983-1984 (2 Folders) (Box 42)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1970-1979 (Box 42)
    - Dean's Advisory Council, 1981-1983 (Box 42)
    - Dean's Advisory Council - Lilly Study, 1982 (Box 42)
    - Dean's Dinner Club, 1983 (Box 42)
    - Department of Religion, 1976-1982 (Box 42)